I will now speak about how we predict
我现在将谈论我们如何预测
that people will play in a game and
人们会玩游戏，
specifically about the concepts of best
特别是关于最佳概念
response and Nash equilibrium now let's
反应和纳什均衡现在让我们
go home were to assume that you are one
回家假设你是一个
of the players and the other players are
的球员和其他球员是
going to play in a way that you know
会以您知道的方式演奏
then we can speak about what is your
那我们可以说说你是什么
best thing to do and we'll call that the
最好的事情，我们称之为
best response and technically speaking
最佳回应，从技术上讲
let's use the following notation let's
让我们使用以下表示法
call AI the action sequence of everybody
把AI称为每个人的行动顺序
except you player I so it's player 1 and
除了你我是玩家1
so on internal player I minus 1 I plus 1
所以内部玩家我减去1我加1
and all the rest so the entire action
其余的一切，整个动作
vector we call it the action profile a
向量，我们将其称为行动概况
is really made up of all those a minus I
真的是由所有减去我的人组成
and your own action with that notation
以及您使用该符号的操作
here's the definition we will say that
这是我们要说的定义
your best response which we'll call AI
您最好的回应，我们称之为AI
star it may not be unique but it's got
明星可能不是唯一的但有
to be part of the set it will call BR
作为集合的一部分，它将调用BR
the best response assuming that all the
假设所有
other agents play is a a - I if it's the
其他特工打的是aa-如果是
case that for any anything you might be
不管你做什么，
thinking of doing a sub I for all a sub
想为所有子项目做一个子项目
I it's got to be the case that your
我一定要这样
utility for playing that in other words
换句话说，实用程序
when you playing AI star and the others
当你玩AI之星和其他人
are playing AI a - I for whatever it is
在玩AI a-我不管
has got to be at least as great as
必须至少与
anything else you might choose a sub I
还有其他你可以选择的子
that's the case we'll say that a AI star
就是这样，我们会说一个AI明星
is a best response very intuitive notion
最好的回应是非常直观的概念
and that would bring us all almost all
那将带给我们几乎所有人
the way there the problem of course is
那里的问题当然是
that you don't know what the others will
你不知道别人会怎么做
do but that's ok because when we use the
可以，但是没关系，因为当我们使用
notion of best response as a building
最佳响应的概念
block to define what we call the Nash
定义我们称为Nash的块
equilibrium and the National Caribbean
均衡与加勒比国家联盟
briefly is a set of acts
简单来说是一套行为
one for each of the agents such that
每个代理一个
each is the best response to the others
每个都是对其他人的最佳回应
specifically we'll look at an action
具体来说，我们来看看一个动作
profile here a a one through a n and
在这里通过一个和一个配置文件
we'll say that it's a Nash equilibrium
我们会说那是纳什均衡
and later on we'll tell you why we call
稍后我们会告诉您为什么我们打电话
it specifically a pure strategy Nash
它专门是一种纯粹的策略纳什
equilibrium if it's the case that for
如果是这样的话
every agent that action a sub I
每个行动一个子我
associate with agent is your best
与代理商合作是您最好的选择
response all the rest
其余所有回应